<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><!--
  Licensed to the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) under one or more
  contributor license agreements.  See the NOTICE file distributed with
  this work for additional information regarding copyright ownership.
  The ASF licenses this file to You under the Apache License, Version 2.0
  (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with
  the License.  You may obtain a copy of the License at
      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  limitations under the License.
--><!--
    This file lists the login identity providers to use when running securely. In order
    to use a specific provider it must be configured here and it's identifier
    must be specified in the nifi.properties file.
--><loginIdentityProviders>
    <!--
        Single User Login Identity Provider supporting automated generation of Username and Password

        The provider will write the following log messages when 'Username' and 'Password' are empty:

        Generated Username [USERNAME]
        Generated Password [PASSWORD]

        The 'Username' will be a random UUID and the 'Password' will be stored using bcrypt hashing
    -->
    <provider>
        <identifier>single-user-provider</identifier>
        <class>org.apache.nifi.authentication.single.user.SingleUserLoginIdentityProvider</class>
        <property name="Username">nifiadmin</property>
        <property name="Password">$2b$12$9PLa8Vhyypf3OaNor0./NukZmjeZ083pJ3oSRsxeT2w.C3Cjl/Y9u</property>
    </provider>
    <!--
        Identity Provider for users logging in with username/password against an LDAP server.
        
        'Authentication Strategy' - How the connection to the LDAP server is authenticated. Possible
            values are ANONYMOUS, SIMPLE, LDAPS, or START_TLS.
        
        'Manager DN' - The DN of the manager that is used to bind to the LDAP server to search for users.
        'Manager Password' - The password of the manager that is used to bind to the LDAP server to
            search for users.
            
        'TLS - Keystore' - Path to the Keystore that is used when connecting to LDAP using LDAPS or START_TLS.
        'TLS - Keystore Password' - Password for the Keystore that is used when connecting to LDAP
            using LDAPS or START_TLS.
        'TLS - Keystore Type' - Type of the Keystore that is used when connecting to LDAP using
            LDAPS or START_TLS such as PKCS12.
        'TLS - Truststore' - Path to the Truststore that is used when connecting to LDAP using LDAPS or START_TLS.
        'TLS - Truststore Password' - Password for the Truststore that is used when connecting to
            LDAP using LDAPS or START_TLS.
        'TLS - Truststore Type' - Type of the Truststore that is used when connecting to LDAP using
            LDAPS or START_TLS such as PKCS12.
        'TLS - Client Auth' - Client authentication policy when connecting to LDAP using LDAPS or START_TLS.
            Possible values are REQUIRED, WANT, NONE.
        'TLS - Protocol' - Protocol to use when connecting to LDAP using LDAPS or START_TLS. (i.e. TLS,
            TLSv1.1, TLSv1.2, etc).
        'TLS - Shutdown Gracefully' - Specifies whether the TLS should be shut down gracefully 
            before the target context is closed. Defaults to false.
            
        'Referral Strategy' - Strategy for handling referrals. Possible values are FOLLOW, IGNORE, THROW.
        'Connect Timeout' - Duration of connect timeout. (i.e. 10 secs).
        'Read Timeout' - Duration of read timeout. (i.e. 10 secs).
       